(Applause)
(تصفيق)
(Music)
(موسيقى)
Angella Ahn: Thank you.
آنجيللا أون: شكرا لكم
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Thank you so much.
أشكركم كثيرا
We are so honored to be here at TEDWomen,
نشعر بالفخر لحضورنا لمؤتمر تيد النسائي
sharing our music with you.
و بمشاركتنا معكم بموسيقانا
What an exciting and inspiring event.
و يا لها من مناسبة ملهمة و مثيرة
What you just heard is "Skylife" by David Balakrishnan.
المقطوعة التى سمعتموها للتو كانت بعنوان "سكاى لايف" من تأليف ديفيد بالاكريشنان
We want to play you one more selection.
نريد ان نعزف لكم واحدة اخرى
It's by Astor Piazzolla, an Argentine composer.
هذه المرة لـ آستور بياتزوللا و هو مؤلف ارجنتيني
And we talk about different ideas --
و نحن نتحدث عن افكار مختلفة--
he had this idea
وكانت لديه تلك الفكرة
that he thought music should be from the heart.
و هى أن الموسيقى يجب ان تنبع من القلب.
This was in the middle of the 20th century
كان ذلك فى منتصف القرن الـ20
when music from the heart, beautiful music,
كانت الموسيقى من القلب, لذلك كانت جميلة,
wasn't the most popular thing in the classical music world.
مقطوعته لم تكن الاشهر فى عالم الموسيقى الكلاسيكية.
It was more atonal and twelve-tone.
كانت تميل اكثر للامقامية و على 12 نغمة.
And he insisted on beautiful music.
فقد كان مصرا على ان تكون الموسيقى جميلة.
So this is "Oblivion" by Astor Piazzolla.
اليكم اذن "اوبليفان"= لـ آستور بياتزوللا.
Thank you.
شكرا لكم
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)